Hello friends, welcome back to VM Energy
Hub. Today we will analyze the financial results of ICICI Lombard for Q3
F25.
Before that, let's
get a little information about the company. Friends,
ICICI Lombard is one of India's leading
private general insurance companies. The company
offers many products. In this, we can
see that it offers products of Motor Health, Crop
Fire, Personal Accident,
Marine, Engineering and Liability
Insurance. The
company has issued a total of 36.2 million policies till March 31, 2024
and has honored 2.9 million
claims.
Here we can see the gross return premium. It has
returned a gross GWP of Rs 5.94 billion.
ICICI Lombard has a total of 312 branches and
13670 employees work.
Here ICICI Lombard company has
presented its financial performance.
In this table, the company has presented its year-on-
year data. Here we
can see the figures are given in rupees in
billions.  I have also presented here.
On the GDPI front, i.e. Gross
Direct
Premium Income, the company is showing a decline of 3 per cent by
reporting Rs 6214 crore in the current quarter.
On the PBT profit before tax front, the company is showing a
decline of 67.3 per cent by reporting Rs 9960 crore. On the profit after tax
front, the company is
showing a growth of 67.5 per cent by reporting Rs 70 crore 24 crore this time.
Overall, the company is
showing a decline on the revenue front and on the
profitability front, the company is
showing good growth.
Next, moving to the company share price
analysis, we can see here that
today's share price of the company has closed at Rs 1955, that is,
with an appreciation of 2.47.
Friends, we all know that today the company has released
its financial report after market close.
Tomorrow we will have to see
how the market is taking it. In the five-day share price
analysis, we can see an
appreciation end at 4.47.  In the one month comparison, we are
able to
see an appreciation of 1.97 percent in the share price
movement. Friends, with this we will
conclude the analysis of the financial results of ACC Lord. Friends, if you
are new then please subscribe to our channel
and if you like our content and efforts
then like it and
share it with your friends. Thank you.